{
    "language": "English",
    "name": "English B1",
    "cards": [
        {"front": "Accept", "back": "Принимать"},
        {"front": "Achieve", "back": "Достигать"},
        {"front": "Act", "back": "Действовать"},
        {"front": "Add", "back": "Добавлять"},
        {"front": "Admire", "back": "Восхищаться"},
        {"front": "Admit", "back": "Признавать"},
        {"front": "Advise", "back": "Советовать"},
        {"front": "Affect", "back": "Влиять"},
        {"front": "Afford", "back": "Позволять себе"},
        {"front": "Agree", "back": "Соглашаться"},
        {"front": "Alert", "back": "Предупреждать"},
        {"front": "Allow", "back": "Разрешать"},
        {"front": "Amuse", "back": "Развлекать"},
        {"front": "Analyze", "back": "Анализировать"},
        {"front": "Announce", "back": "Объявлять"},
        {"front": "Annoy", "back": "Раздражать"},
        {"front": "Answer", "back": "Отвечать"},
        {"front": "Apologize", "back": "Извиняться"},
        {"front": "Appear", "back": "Появляться"},
        {"front": "Appreciate", "back": "Ценить"},
        {"front": "Approach", "back": "Приближаться"},
        {"front": "Approve", "back": "Одобрять"},
        {"front": "Argue", "back": "Спорить"},
        {"front": "Arise", "back": "Возникать"},
        {"front": "Arrange", "back": "Организовывать"},
        {"front": "Arrive", "back": "Прибывать"},
        {"front": "Ask", "back": "Спрашивать"},
        {"front": "Attack", "back": "Атаковать"},
        {"front": "Attempt", "back": "Пытаться"},
        {"front": "Attend", "back": "Посещать"},
        {"front": "Attract", "back": "Привлекать"},
        {"front": "Avoid", "back": "Избегать"},
        {"front": "Bake", "back": "Печь"},
        {"front": "Balance", "back": "Уравновешивать"},
        {"front": "Ban", "back": "Запрещать"},
        {"front": "Bang", "back": "Стучать"},
        {"front": "Bare", "back": "Обнажать"},
        {"front": "Bathe", "back": "Купаться"},
        {"front": "Battle", "back": "Сражаться"},
        {"front": "Bear", "back": "Выносить"},
        {"front": "Beat", "back": "Бить"},
        {"front": "Become", "back": "Становиться"},
        {"front": "Beg", "back": "Умолять"},
        {"front": "Behave", "back": "Вести себя"},
        {"front": "Believe", "back": "Верить"},
        {"front": "Belong", "back": "Принадлежать"},
        {"front": "Bend", "back": "Сгибать"},
        {"front": "Bet", "back": "Держать пари"},
        {"front": "Bite", "back": "Кусать"},
        {"front": "Blame", "back": "Винить"},
        {"front": "Bleed", "back": "Кровоточить"},
        {"front": "Bless", "back": "Благословлять"},
        {"front": "Blind", "back": "Ослеплять"},
        {"front": "Blink", "back": "Моргать"},
        {"front": "Block", "back": "Блокировать"},
        {"front": "Blow", "back": "Дуть"},
        {"front": "Boil", "back": "Кипятить"},
        {"front": "Bomb", "back": "Бомбить"},
        {"front": "Book", "back": "Бронировать"},
        {"front": "Bore", "back": "Надоедать"},
        {"front": "Borrow", "back": "Одалживать"},
        {"front": "Bother", "back": "Беспокоить"},
        {"front": "Bounce", "back": "Подпрыгивать"},
        {"front": "Bow", "back": "Кланяться"},
        {"front": "Box", "back": "Боксировать"},
        {"front": "Brake", "back": "Тормозить"},
        {"front": "Branch", "back": "Разветвляться"},
        {"front": "Breathe", "back": "Дышать"},
        {"front": "Breed", "back": "Разводить"},
        {"front": "Bring", "back": "Приносить"},
        {"front": "Broadcast", "back": "Транслировать"},
        {"front": "Brush", "back": "Чистить щеткой"},
        {"front": "Bubble", "back": "Пузыриться"},
        {"front": "Build", "back": "Строить"},
        {"front": "Bump", "back": "Сталкиваться"},
        {"front": "Burn", "back": "Гореть"},
        {"front": "Burst", "back": "Лопаться"},
        {"front": "Bury", "back": "Хоронить"},
        {"front": "Calculate", "back": "Вычислять"},
        {"front": "Call", "back": "Звонить"},
        {"front": "Camp", "back": "Разбивать лагерь"},
        {"front": "Care", "back": "Заботиться"},
        {"front": "Carry", "back": "Нести"},
        {"front": "Carve", "back": "Вырезать"},
        {"front": "Cause", "back": "Вызывать"},
        {"front": "Challenge", "back": "Вызывать на дуэль"},
        {"front": "Change", "back": "Менять"},
        {"front": "Charge", "back": "Заряжать"},
        {"front": "Chase", "back": "Гнаться"},
        {"front": "Chat", "back": "Болтать"},
        {"front": "Check", "back": "Проверять"},
        {"front": "Cheer", "back": "Подбадривать"},
        {"front": "Chew", "back": "Жевать"},
        {"front": "Choose", "back": "Выбирать"},
        {"front": "Claim", "back": "Требовать"},
        {"front": "Clap", "back": "Хлопать"},
        {"front": "Clean", "back": "Чистить"},
        {"front": "Clear", "back": "Очищать"},
        {"front": "Climb", "back": "Взбираться"},
        {"front": "Close", "back": "Закрывать"},
        {"front": "Collect", "back": "Коллекционировать"},
        {"front": "Come", "back": "Приходить"},
        {"front": "Complain", "back": "Жаловаться"},
        {"front": "Complete", "back": "Завершать"},
        {"front": "Concentrate", "back": "Концентрироваться"},
        {"front": "Concern", "back": "Беспокоить"},
        {"front": "Confess", "back": "Признаваться"},
        {"front": "Confuse", "back": "Путать"},
        {"front": "Connect", "back": "Соединять"},
        {"front": "Consider", "back": "Обдумывать"},
        {"front": "Consist", "back": "Состоять"},
        {"front": "Contact", "back": "Связываться"},
        {"front": "Contain", "back": "Содержать"},
        {"front": "Continue", "back": "Продолжать"},
        {"front": "Control", "back": "Контролировать"},
        {"front": "Cook", "back": "Готовить"},
        {"front": "Copy", "back": "Копировать"},
        {"front": "Correct", "back": "Исправлять"},
        {"front": "Cost", "back": "Стоить"},
        {"front": "Cough", "back": "Кашлять"},
        {"front": "Count", "back": "Считать"},
        {"front": "Cover", "back": "Накрывать"},
        {"front": "Crash", "back": "Разбиваться"},
        {"front": "Crawl", "back": "Ползать"},
        {"front": "Create", "back": "Создавать"},
        {"front": "Cross", "back": "Пересекать"},
        {"front": "Cry", "back": "Плакать"},
        {"front": "Cure", "back": "Лечить"},
        {"front": "Curve", "back": "Изгибаться"},
        {"front": "Cut", "back": "Резать"},
        {"front": "Cycle", "back": "Ездить на велосипеде"},
        {"front": "Damage", "back": "Повреждать"},
        {"front": "Dance", "back": "Танцевать"},
        {"front": "Dare", "back": "Осмеливаться"},
        {"front": "Deal", "back": "Иметь дело"},
        {"front": "Decide", "back": "Решать"},
        {"front": "Decrease", "back": "Уменьшать"},
        {"front": "Defeat", "back": "Побеждать"},
        {"front": "Defend", "back": "Защищать"},
        {"front": "Delay", "back": "Задерживать"},
        {"front": "Deliver", "back": "Доставлять"},
        {"front": "Depend", "back": "Зависеть"},
        {"front": "Describe", "back": "Описывать"},
        {"front": "Desert", "back": "Покидать"},
        {"front": "Deserve", "back": "Заслуживать"},
        {"front": "Destroy", "back": "Уничтожать"},
        {"front": "Develop", "back": "Развивать"},
        {"front": "Disagree", "back": "Не соглашаться"},
        {"front": "Disappear", "back": "Исчезать"},
        {"front": "Disapprove", "back": "Не одобрять"},
        {"front": "Discover", "back": "Открывать"},
        {"front": "Discuss", "back": "Обсуждать"},
        {"front": "Dislike", "back": "Не любить"},
        {"front": "Divide", "back": "Делить"},
        {"front": "Do", "back": "Делать"},
        {"front": "Doubt", "back": "Сомневаться"},
        {"front": "Drag", "back": "Тащить"},
        {"front": "Drain", "back": "Сливать"},
        {"front": "Draw", "back": "Рисовать"},
        {"front": "Dream", "back": "Мечтать"},
        {"front": "Dress", "back": "Одеваться"},
        {"front": "Drink", "back": "Пить"},
        {"front": "Drive", "back": "Водить"},
        {"front": "Drop", "back": "Бросать"},
        {"front": "Drown", "back": "Тонеть"},
        {"front": "Dry", "back": "Сушить"},
        {"front": "Earn", "back": "Зарабатывать"},
        {"front": "Educate", "back": "Обучать"},
        {"front": "Employ", "back": "Нанимать"},
        {"front": "Encourage", "back": "Поощрять"},
        {"front": "End", "back": "Заканчивать"},
        {"front": "Enjoy", "back": "Наслаждаться"},
        {"front": "Enter", "back": "Входить"},
        {"front": "Escape", "back": "Сбегать"},
        {"front": "Examine", "back": "Исследовать"},
        {"front": "Exist", "back": "Существовать"},
        {"front": "Expand", "back": "Расширять"},
        {"front": "Expect", "back": "Ожидать"},
        {"front": "Explain", "back": "Объяснять"},
        {"front": "Explode", "back": "Взрываться"},
        {"front": "Extend", "back": "Продлевать"},
        {"front": "Face", "back": "Сталкиваться"},
        {"front": "Fail", "back": "Проваливаться"},
        {"front": "Fall", "back": "Падать"},
        {"front": "Fasten", "back": "Пристегивать"},
        {"front": "Fear", "back": "Бояться"},
        {"front": "Feed", "back": "Кормить"},
        {"front": "Feel", "back": "Чувствовать"},
        {"front": "Fight", "back": "Бороться"},
        {"front": "Fill", "back": "Заполнять"},
        {"front": "Find", "back": "Находить"},
        {"front": "Finish", "back": "Заканчивать"},
        {"front": "Fit", "back": "Подходить"},
        {"front": "Fix", "back": "Чинить"},
        {"front": "Flash", "back": "Сверкать"},
        {"front": "Float", "back": "Плавать"},
        {"front": "Fold", "back": "Складывать"},
        {"front": "Follow", "back": "Следовать"},
        {"front": "Force", "back": "Принуждать"},
        {"front": "Form", "back": "Формировать"},
        {"front": "Found", "back": "Основать"},
        {"front": "Frame", "back": "Обрамлять"},
        {"front": "Freeze", "back": "Замерзать"},
        {"front": "Frighten", "back": "Пугать"},
        {"front": "Fry", "back": "Жарить"},
        {"front": "Gather", "back": "Собирать"},
        {"front": "Get", "back": "Получать"},
        {"front": "Give", "back": "Давать"},
        {"front": "Go", "back": "Идти"},
        {"front": "Grow", "back": "Расти"},
        {"front": "Guess", "back": "Угадывать"},
        {"front": "Guide", "back": "Вести"},
        {"front": "Handle", "back": "Справляться"},
        {"front": "Hang", "back": "Вешать"},
        {"front": "Happen", "back": "Случаться"},
        {"front": "Hate", "back": "Ненавидеть"},
        {"front": "Have", "back": "Иметь"},
        {"front": "Hear", "back": "Слышать"},
        {"front": "Help", "back": "Помогать"},
        {"front": "Hide", "back": "Прятать"},
        {"front": "Hit", "back": "Ударять"},
        {"front": "Hold", "back": "Держать"},
        {"front": "Hope", "back": "Надеяться"},
        {"front": "Hurt", "back": "Причинять боль"},
        {"front": "Identify", "back": "Идентифицировать"},
        {"front": "Ignore", "back": "Игнорировать"},
        {"front": "Imagine", "back": "Воображать"},
        {"front": "Improve", "back": "Улучшать"},
        {"front": "Include", "back": "Включать"},
        {"front": "Increase", "back": "Увеличивать"},
        {"front": "Influence", "back": "Влиять"},
        {"front": "Inform", "back": "Сообщать"},
        {"front": "Insist", "back": "Настаивать"},
        {"front": "Introduce", "back": "Знакомить"},
        {"front": "Invite", "back": "Приглашать"},
        {"front": "Involve", "back": "Вовлекать"},
        {"front": "Iron", "back": "Гладить"},
        {"front": "Join", "back": "Присоединяться"},
        {"front": "Jump", "back": "Прыгать"},
        {"front": "Keep", "back": "Хранить"},
        {"front": "Kick", "back": "Пинать"},
        {"front": "Kill", "back": "Убивать"},
        {"front": "Kiss", "back": "Целовать"},
        {"front": "Know", "back": "Знать"},
        {"front": "Laugh", "back": "Смеяться"},
        {"front": "Learn", "back": "Учить"},
        {"front": "Leave", "back": "Покидать"},
        {"front": "Lend", "back": "Одалживать"},
        {"front": "Let", "back": "Позволять"},
        {"front": "Lie", "back": "Лгать"},
        {"front": "Like", "back": "Нравиться"},
        {"front": "Listen", "back": "Слушать"},
        {"front": "Live", "back": "Жить"},
        {"front": "Look", "back": "Смотреть"},
        {"front": "Lose", "back": "Терять"},
        {"front": "Love", "back": "Любить"},
        {"front": "Make", "back": "Делать"},
        {"front": "Manage", "back": "Управлять"},
        {"front": "Mean", "back": "Значить"},
        {"front": "Meet", "back": "Встречать"},
        {"front": "Mention", "back": "Упоминать"},
        {"front": "Miss", "back": "Скучать"},
        {"front": "Mix", "back": "Смешивать"},
        {"front": "Move", "back": "Двигаться"},
        {"front": "Must", "back": "Должен"},
        {"front": "Need", "back": "Нуждаться"},
        {"front": "Notice", "back": "Замечать"},
        {"front": "Obey", "back": "Повиноваться"},
        {"front": "Offer", "back": "Предлагать"},
        {"front": "Open", "back": "Открывать"},
        {"front": "Order", "back": "Заказывать"},
        {"front": "Owe", "back": "Быть должным"},
        {"front": "Own", "back": "Владеть"},
        {"front": "Pass", "back": "Проходить"},
        {"front": "Pay", "back": "Платить"},
        {"front": "Pick", "back": "Выбирать"},
        {"front": "Place", "back": "Помещать"},
        {"front": "Plan", "back": "Планировать"},
        {"front": "Plant", "back": "Сажать"},
        {"front": "Play", "back": "Играть"},
        {"front": "Please", "back": "Пожалуйста"},
        {"front": "Point", "back": "Указывать"},
        {"front": "Prefer", "back": "Предпочитать"},
        {"front": "Prepare", "back": "Готовить"},
        {"front": "Press", "back": "Нажимать"},
        {"front": "Pretend", "back": "Притворяться"},
        {"front": "Prevent", "back": "Предотвращать"},
        {"front": "Promise", "back": "Обещать"},
        {"front": "Protect", "back": "Защищать"},
        {"front": "Prove", "back": "Доказывать"},
        {"front": "Pull", "back": "Тянуть"},
        {"front": "Punish", "back": "Наказывать"},
        {"front": "Push", "back": "Толкать"},
        {"front": "Put", "back": "Класть"},
        {"front": "Question", "back": "Спрашивать"},
        {"front": "Race", "back": "Гоняться"},
        {"front": "Rain", "back": "Идти (о дожде)"},
        {"front": "Reach", "back": "Достигать"},
        {"front": "Read", "back": "Читать"},
        {"front": "Realize", "back": "Осознавать"},
        {"front": "Receive", "back": "Получать"},
        {"front": "Recognize", "back": "Узнавать"},
        {"front": "Record", "back": "Записывать"},
        {"front": "Reduce", "back": "Уменьшать"},
        {"front": "Refuse", "back": "Отказываться"},
        {"front": "Regret", "back": "Сожалеть"},
        {"front": "Relax", "back": "Расслабляться"},
        {"front": "Remember", "back": "Помнить"},
        {"front": "Remind", "back": "Напоминать"},
        {"front": "Remove", "back": "Удалять"},
        {"front": "Repair", "back": "Чинить"},
        {"front": "Repeat", "back": "Повторять"},
        {"front": "Replace", "back": "Заменять"},
        {"front": "Reply", "back": "Отвечать"},
        {"front": "Report", "back": "Сообщать"},
        {"front": "Request", "back": "Просить"},
        {"front": "Rescue", "back": "Спасать"},
        {"front": "Retire", "back": "Уходить на пенсию"},
        {"front": "Return", "back": "Возвращаться"},
        {"front": "Review", "back": "Просматривать"},
        {"front": "Ride", "back": "Ездить верхом"},
        {"front": "Ring", "back": "Звонить"},
        {"front": "Rise", "back": "Подниматься"},
        {"front": "Risk", "back": "Рисковать"},
        {"front": "Roll", "back": "Катиться"},
        {"front": "Run", "back": "Бежать"},
        {"front": "Save", "back": "Сохранять"},
        {"front": "Say", "back": "Говорить"},
        {"front": "See", "back": "Видеть"},
        {"front": "Seem", "back": "Казаться"},
        {"front": "Sell", "back": "Продавать"},
        {"front": "Send", "back": "Отправлять"},
        {"front": "Serve", "back": "Подавать"},
        {"front": "Set", "back": "Устанавливать"},
        {"front": "Settle", "back": "Улаживать"},
        {"front": "Sew", "back": "Шить"},
        {"front": "Shake", "back": "Трясти"},
        {"front": "Share", "back": "Делиться"},
        {"front": "Shave", "back": "Брить"},
        {"front": "Shine", "back": "Сиять"},
        {"front": "Shoot", "back": "Стрелять"},
        {"front": "Show", "back": "Показывать"},
        {"front": "Shut", "back": "Закрывать"},
        {"front": "Sing", "back": "Петь"},
        {"front": "Sink", "back": "Тонеть"},
        {"front": "Sit", "back": "Сидеть"},
        {"front": "Sleep", "back": "Спать"},
        {"front": "Smell", "back": "Пахнуть"},
        {"front": "Smile", "back": "Улыбаться"},
        {"front": "Smoke", "back": "Курить"},
        {"front": "Sound", "back": "Звучать"},
        {"front": "Speak", "back": "Говорить"},
        {"front": "Spell", "back": "Произносить по буквам"},
        {"front": "Spend", "back": "Тратить"},
        {"front": "Spill", "back": "Проливать"},
        {"front": "Split", "back": "Раскалывать"},
        {"front": "Spoil", "back": "Портить"},
        {"front": "Spread", "back": "Распространять"},
        {"front": "Stand", "back": "Стоять"},
        {"front": "Start", "back": "Начинать"},
        {"front": "Stay", "back": "Оставаться"},
        {"front": "Steal", "back": "Красть"},
        {"front": "Stick", "back": "Приклеивать"},
        {"front": "Stop", "back": "Останавливать"},
        {"front": "Study", "back": "Учить"},
        {"front": "Succeed", "back": "Преуспевать"},
        {"front": "Suggest", "back": "Предлагать"},
        {"front": "Supply", "back": "Поставлять"},
        {"front": "Support", "back": "Поддерживать"},
        {"front": "Suppose", "back": "Предполагать"},
        {"front": "Surprise", "back": "Удивлять"},
        {"front": "Survive", "back": "Выживать"},
        {"front": "Swim", "back": "Плавать"},
        {"front": "Take", "back": "Брать"},
        {"front": "Talk", "back": "Говорить"},
        {"front": "Taste", "back": "Пробовать"},
        {"front": "Teach", "back": "Учить"},
        {"front": "Tear", "back": "Рвать"},
        {"front": "Tell", "back": "Рассказывать"},
        {"front": "Tend", "back": "Иметь тенденцию"},
        {"front": "Test", "back": "Проверять"},
        {"front": "Thank", "back": "Благодарить"},
        {"front": "Think", "back": "Думать"},
        {"front": "Throw", "back": "Бросать"},
        {"front": "Touch", "back": "Прикасаться"},
        {"front": "Train", "back": "Тренировать"},
        {"front": "Travel", "back": "Путешествовать"},
        {"front": "Treat", "back": "Лечить"},
        {"front": "Trust", "back": "Доверять"},
        {"front": "Try", "back": "Пробовать"},
        {"front": "Turn", "back": "Поворачивать"},
        {"front": "Understand", "back": "Понимать"},
        {"front": "Use", "back": "Использовать"},
        {"front": "Visit", "back": "Посещать"},
        {"front": "Wait", "back": "Ждать"},
        {"front": "Wake", "back": "Просыпаться"},
        {"front": "Walk", "back": "Гулять"},
        {"front": "Want", "back": "Хотеть"},
        {"front": "Warn", "back": "Предупреждать"},
        {"front": "Wash", "back": "Мыть"},
        {"front": "Waste", "back": "Тратить впустую"},
        {"front": "Watch", "back": "Смотреть"},
        {"front": "Wave", "back": "Махать"},
        {"front": "Wear", "back": "Носить"},
        {"front": "Weep", "back": "Плакать"},
        {"front": "Weigh", "back": "Взвешивать"},
        {"front": "Wet", "back": "Мочить"},
        {"front": "Win", "back": "Выигрывать"},
        {"front": "Wish", "back": "Желать"},
        {"front": "Wonder", "back": "Интересоваться"},
        {"front": "Work", "back": "Работать"},
        {"front": "Worry", "back": "Беспокоиться"},
        {"front": "Write", "back": "Писать"},
        {"front": "Walk", "back": "Ходить"},
        {"front": "Wear", "back": "Носить (одежду)"},
        {"front": "Welcome", "back": "Приветствовать"},
        {"front": "Withdraw", "back": "Снимать (деньги)"},
        {"front": "Wrap", "back": "Оборачивать"},
        {"front": "Apply", "back": "Применять"},
        {"front": "Assume", "back": "Предполагать"},
        {"front": "Bake", "back": "Выпекать"},
        {"front": "Balance", "back": "Балансировать"},
        {"front": "Bend", "back": "Наклонять"},
        {"front": "Borrow", "back": "Занимать"},
        {"front": "Brush", "back": "Чистить (щеткой)"},
        {"front": "Buy", "back": "Покупать"},
        {"front": "Carry", "back": "Носить"},
        {"front": "Catch", "back": "Ловить"},
        {"front": "Climb", "back": "Лазить"},
        {"front": "Collect", "back": "Собирать"},
        {"front": "Concentrate", "back": "Сосредоточиваться"},
        {"front": "Confirm", "back": "Подтверждать"},
        {"front": "Consider", "back": "Рассматривать"},
        {"front": "Cover", "back": "Покрывать"},
        {"front": "Design", "back": "Проектировать"},
        {"front": "Dress", "back": "Одевать"},
        {"front": "Drop", "back": "Падать"},
        {"front": "Eat", "back": "Есть"},
        {"front": "Fly", "back": "Летать"},
        {"front": "Force", "back": "Заставлять"},
        {"front": "Forget", "back": "Забывать"},
        {"front": "Forgive", "back": "Прощать"},
        {"front": "Guess", "back": "Догадываться"},
        {"front": "Happen", "back": "Происходить"},
        {"front": "Hurt", "back": "Ранить"},
        {"front": "Identify", "back": "Опознавать"},
        {"front": "Imagine", "back": "Представлять"},
        {"front": "Inform", "back": "Информировать"},
        {"front": "Introduce", "back": "Представлять"},
        {"front": "Keep", "back": "Держать"},
        {"front": "Lend", "back": "Одолжить"},
        {"front": "Lie", "back": "Лежать / Врать"},
        {"front": "Marry", "back": "Жениться / Выходить замуж"},
        {"front": "Mean", "back": "Означать"},
        {"front": "Measure", "back": "Измерять"},
        {"front": "Miss", "back": "Скучать / Пропускать"},
        {"front": "Notice", "back": "Заметить"},
        {"front": "Organize", "back": "Организовывать"},
        {"front": "Perform", "back": "Выполнять"},
        {"front": "Present", "back": "Представлять"},
        {"front": "Produce", "back": "Производить"},
        {"front": "Provide", "back": "Обеспечивать"},
        {"front": "Raise", "back": "Поднимать"},
        {"front": "Recognize", "back": "Признавать"},
        {"front": "Remember", "back": "Запоминать"},
        {"front": "Report", "back": "Докладывать"},
        {"front": "Require", "back": "Требовать"},
        {"front": "Return", "back": "Возвращать"},
        {"front": "Sign", "back": "Подписывать"},
        {"front": "Stop", "back": "Останавливаться"},
        {"front": "Study", "back": "Учиться"},
        {"front": "Talk", "back": "Разговаривать"},
        {"front": "Test", "back": "Тестировать"},
        {"front": "Try", "back": "Пытаться"},
        {"front": "Write", "back": "Писать"}
    ]
}
